Hello, I am Sanjay, and you are watching the
technical channel. Friends, if you are a health
worker or engaged in some such lower service from
where you are not able to take even a day's leave under this Lokpal,
you are
not allowed to take leave because the government has announced
that all the bank workers who are
working in hospitals etc. or anywhere where they have to
deal with corona patients, whether it is a
quarantine center or a hospital, then
in such a situation, you are
not allowed by the government to take even a day's leave.
In such a situation, you and your family must be
worried about your health and your condition. In
such a situation, if you
feel the need for health insurance, friends,
in both these insurance options offered by Flipkart, there is
no health checkup, there is no documentation,
you just have to take your smartphone in your hands
and from here the whole work is
completed within 5 minutes. So,
we will talk about this in detail and quickly
start the video, introduce it and
you guys will see it.
Look, subscribe and we'll meet
after the intro.
So friends, to know the details about the two
health programs that Flipkart has introduced to us, let's go to the
Flipkart application and from there we will
know what are its benefits, how many
plans are there, how many are available for dengue,
so for this information, let's quickly start
its application, so let's go
straight to your Flipkart application and from
here we will set it up and in the top left
corner, there is 'N' and when we
go here, we see that under flights, hotels and buses,
you see insurance,
next to it is written 'Nuke' in red color, let's
setup it with this from here, you will see two
options, here it is written '
Stay Safe, Stay Protected, Get Health
Insurance Cover up to Rs. 1 Lakh for Rs. 209,
Medical Test Stand Digital Policy' and
here we click on 'No More',
go inside it and here we
get to see some different types of plans, which are
written at the top, 'No Medical
Test Stand Digital Policy' is Claim
Process' and here at the bottom, we get some different types of
plans which are 159, 511  Of
and if I go inside it, then of
159, then here I get
2501 positive diagnosis of combination
coronavirus that your positive diagnosis has come home,
in that case you will get Rs. 25000, you will get
tele consultation,
ambulance assistance and available for
a sweet 18275 for this, there will be a TDS
cancellation policy, its validity will be one year, so
you get so many things for 115, let me
see what is its 511 plan, so on
tapping inside it, I
get that if your diagnosis comes positive,
then now you will get a claim of up to one lakh rupees,
one percent of which will be there will be
for ambulance, no limit on
room rent and this is
covering you for 30 days before and seven days after going to the hospital,
this is for 18 years and there is a 15 day
cancellation policy, there is also a one year skin
validity and let's talk about 1267 Russia
policy  So on tapping inside this, you will
see that here you get full ₹3
on hospitalization positive diagnosis and
one percent is available on your ambulance, no
limit rent and ICU, there is no
limit for ICU, so from this day before
till 30 days after, this is also for 18 years old
friends, this has a cancellation
policy and it also has a validity of one year
and if you look here below all this, then it
is written here '
Important Singh', in this you have been
given some details etc. in which it has been told
that you do not have to give any medical proof
on time for the purchase and it has been given in it
that
you can recharge only one policy from more than one Flipkart account
and they are famous for themselves
and here some toll free numbers have been given
from ICICI Lombard for customer support and
inside all this now let's go to the readable fax option,
so on clicking here we get
some of its policies here, so if
I will tell you guys for so long then maybe  This will be a bit
long, so you can
go directly to your Flipkart app and read it.
For which people is it necessary,
or I can scroll it up and down slowly. From
here, you can also read it by pausing it. There will be
some main points, I will
tell you about them right now. It is here in this way,
if you need it, you can read it here by
pausing it and wherever you need it.
Everything is given in it. Will there be a
grave inside it, will there be a grave inside it, will there be a
life for it, and who
cannot apply for it. Half the
things have been explained in detail in it, how and
what facilities will be given to you in it, so
wherever you need all these things,
you can read it by
my voice. First, I am slowly
scrolling it and it has ended here
and I hope you
liked this information and you must have understood
everything. So, if you feel
that you need health insurance,
you are feeling trapped somewhere
because in such a time, neither any student
advisor is coming to you nor  You are not
able to go to any insurance office and
you feel that you should take health insurance, in
such a situation it is in your hands,
quickly pick up the phone and get started,
before leaving please like this video and
subscribe to the channel, see you
in the upcoming video, till then
Namaskar